And I think I had a commander that said early ... We had an info meeting -
- I don't know if you had it too?
- Yes we had.
Before starting your first day.
Then he said like this
"The better trained you are the easier it will be mental"
Because then you have time to think, then you are not as exhausted.
So it is, absolutely!
I remember one of the mental things like me -
- In the beginning, during the undergraduate education anyway.
It was special when we were out in the field.
That when you were done for the day and would go to the tent site
But this is what will be obvious later.
We had a lot ... you can help mentally too.
Just asking someone "How's it going?", "How are you?"
“Do you have clean socks?
"Do you want a pair of socks?".
Only something like that can make a huge difference to someone's well -being.
Okay, then we'll see!
Is it a lot of peer pressure and freezing?
So, I would say that the commanders are really good at seeing through that.
And what I have experienced is in that case
That someone has flagged for it.
And said well in advance, "now someone is really naughty here"
And then they have put their foot down immediately.
We also had defense health, which is like the Armed Forces health center.
- A small hospital.
- A little hospital yes!
There you had to visit the doctor.
I know I had sometimes -
–Heelne inflammation from marching, and then they realized that
"Okay, but then maybe you need to have soles"
And then they put it in.
And it got much better ...
... and solved the problem.
So there are doctors to visit ...
... and you get to flag them if it is something you feel bad about.
Okay, the next question!